Guide to the Tenneco Energy History Records
University of Houston Libraries
- Oversized
  - Tenneco Publications
    - E&P Update, Jan, Aug-Oct, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 7)